const fetchAllResult = {
  command: "SELECT", // Care-ish
  rowCount: 12, // Care-ish
  oid: null,
  rows: [
    // MOST IMPORTANT ROWS
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Knock knock, whos there, to who",
      answer: "no, to whom",
      rating: 3,
      author_id: 1,
      joke_id: 1,
      name: "AFrancis",
      funny: true,
      description: "Oh boy, he is a teacher",
    },
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Why do programmers mix hallowen and christmas",
      answer: "because OCT 31 === DEC 25",
      rating: 5,
      author_id: 1,
      name: "AFrancis",
      funny: true,
      description: "Oh boy, he is a teacher",
    },
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is small, green and goes up and down?",
      answer: "A green pea in an elevator",
      rating: 4.46,
      author_id: 1,
      name: "AFrancis",
      funny: true,
      description: "Oh boy, he is a teacher",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "How is a bouncer at a club like a dish soap?",
      answer: "They both DETER GENTS",
      rating: 5,
      author_id: 2,
      name: "Paul",
      funny: true,
      description: "A student in march01",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "What do you call a belt made out of watches?",
      answer: "A waist of time.",
      rating: 5,
      author_id: 3,
      name: "Mike",
      funny: true,
      description: "A student in march01",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "You know you should knock on your fridge door before opening it",
      answer: "There might by a salad dressing",
      rating: 5,
      author_id: 4,
      name: "Grigor",
      funny: true,
      description: "A student in march29",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Did you hear about the monkeys who shared an Amazon account?",
      answer: "They were Prime mates.",
      rating: 4,
      author_id: 6,
      name: "Anton",
      funny: true,
      description: "A student in july 19",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Why did the chicken cross the road?",
      answer: "Because there was a green light",
      rating: 4.46,
      author_id: 7,
      name: "Aphy",
      funny: true,
      description: "A student in july 19",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "What do you call a fly without wings?",
      answer: "A walk",
      rating: 5,
      author_id: 9,
      name: "Dusty",
      funny: true,
      description: "A student in nov 22",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "Did you recognize that 2022 sound like 2020 too",
      answer: null,
      rating: 3,
      author_id: 10,
      name: "Olga",
      funny: true,
      description: "A student in nov 22",
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "What do you call a bear with no teeth?",
      answer: "A Gummy Bear",
      rating: 4,
      author_id: 11,
      name: "Luciana",
      funny: true,
      description: "A student in nov 22",
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "What do you call an indecisive bee?",
      answer: " A maybe.",
      rating: 5,
      author_id: 12,
      name: "Aldwin",
      funny: true,
      description: "A student in sept 19",
    },
  ],
};
